<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Life Hack</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Blank</string>
    <string name="tips11">\t\tSave time in the morning by freezing shots of black coffee and black tea in advance. Just pop one in your mug and top up with boiling water for the perfect cup every time</string>
    <string name="tips12">\t\tWant to drink your morning cup of hot coffee or tea straight away? Prepare some coffee and tea ice cubes in advance and pop a couple of cubes in your mug to cool it down without diluting the taste</string>
    <string name="tips_21">\t\tEnjoy ice cold water all day long by filling a water bottle half way and freezing it. Then, just top up with water throughout the day, it will be cool and refreshing almost instantly and is an especially handy trick if you are on a day trip.</string>
    <string name="tips_22">\t\t if you’re not travelling, you can still get the most of your summer with these lifehacks, whether you’re having a BBQ at home or freshening up your wardrobe</string>
    <string name='tips_31'>\t\tTea Bags is one of the ingredients and spices that can reduce moisture and neutralize odors, do not need to use a teabag new if shame to use new, disposable tea bag former can but must be dried first, input into a shoe insole can be one or two teabag.</string>
    <string name="tips_32">\t\tDeodorise trainers or canvas pumps when travelling by placing a fresh tea bag in them overnight. In the morning, they will smell gorgeously fresh</string>
    <string name="tips_4">\t\tNo need to buy an expensive phone holder for your car. Just grab a few household items and make one yourself</string>
    <string name="tips_42">\t\tYou only need to provide paper clips and rubber bands to make a phone holder. Rubber bands used to hold the phone in both the handle clips which phone would be placed in between. Better if you use more than one rubber band to the holder so that more powerful.</string>
    <string name="tips_5">\t\tTips when serving pizza to your friends without having to use a plate or cutlery that is where you have to wash it. Simply use cardboard pizza is cut into pieces as pieces of pizza containers.</string>
    <string name="tips_52">\t\tAfter you finished, you do not inconvenience to wash the dishes. Container just stay put in the bin. It is simple</string>
</resources>
